Matías Ponce /

Associate

Practice Area: Regulatory and Corporate Law

matias.ponce@ocl.cl

Matías has focused on regulatory and corporate law and has been counsel in administrative proceedings, in the defense against administrative penalties, in the review and processing of permits and concessions with government authorities, in public tenders and appeals of administrative decisions. He has also been counsel in consumer matters to be defended before the courts, in requests for official information, in collective mediation, marketing and advertising.

WORK HISTORY

2017 - present / Ovalle Consejeros Legales

2013 - 2014 / Barros & Errázuriz Abogados

EDUCATION

B.A. in Legal and Social Sciences, University of Chile, graduating summa cum laude. Admissions: 2015

Recent Changes in Family Law, School of Law, University of Chile, 2017-2018

ACADEMIC EXPERIENCE

Aid in the Civil Law Course, University of Chile

PUBLICATIONS

- Conference Paper on "Contracts and Public Order: Moving towards a new relationship." Second place in the Private Law Student Congress, Pontifical Catholic University of Chile.
- Article published in the Review of the UC Law Course Aids Association.
- Paper on "Divorce in Chilean Law: A critical analysis and elements for an appropriate regulation."
- 17th Seminar on Current Events in the Law, School of Law, University of Valparaiso. This paper will be published in a special edition dedicated to the 17th Seminar on Current Events in the Law of the Philosophy and Legal Science Review of the University of Valparaíso.
- "Article 2-bis of the Consumer Protection Law: Critical and comparative analysis." This paper will be published in a special edition on the 17th Seminar of Current Events in the Philosophy and Legal Science Review of the University of Valparaíso.

LANGUAGES

Spanish and English